tutorialsplane.com 2019-01-03

# Privacy Policy - Tutorialsplane

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number on tutorialsplane. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes we use cookies to personalize the user experience.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.tutorialsplane.com  
331-3f vaishali sec 3  
ghaziabad, N/A 201010, Email- contact@tutorialsplane.com.
